That someone has said the truth, there is
only and only lies in the market and only and
only useless advertisements and a big
example of that is in front of you, Emami brand
's seven oils in one hair oil, yes now as you
can see, non-stick hair oil, strong
inside, set outside, let's see the nice little one on the back
side, it is written make hair up
228 stronger, that is, it will make your hair 20
* strong, set for the whole day,
okay, if seen inside the level, then
what is the problem in it, you get amla to connect
with almond, which looks at the amount in jaoba and life and
many more, okay, it looks like walnut,
okay, if you talk about the less portion, then
if you can see the less portion, then
all these things are only and only
less than five percent, and what is there, then only
and only paraffin liquid form 93.92 to
0.4 percent, so please try this type of product code
totally, do not get carried away by such
products